

Alberto Hurtado Ruiz

Nationality: Spanish | Email address: alberto.hurt.99@gmail.com

Address: Madrid, Spain (Home)

About me:

I am a full stack developer specialized in Scala and Angular with MongoDB. I am passionate about quality software craftmanship following good practices and agile methodologies.

My programming languages of preference are: Scala, Java, Typescript and Python

I have experience with AWS from my internship at Amazon

WORK EXPERIENCE

19/07/2021 - CURRENT Madrid, Spain

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ENGINEER ALTEN DELIVERY CENTER (MACQ CLIENT)

Work as a fullstack developer consultant in an international project about smart mobility inside of an agile team. My responsability is to deliver new features and maintain a web application with high volumes of real time data, focusing on making it performant and following coding best practices.

07/02/2021 - 19/06/2021 Madrid, Spain

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN IF INTELLIGENT FULFILLMENT

As part of the development team of a start up, my responsibilities consisted in assisting the senior developer in the design of the data model, architecture and implementation of the business logic to achieve scheduled delivery in the main e-commerce platforms.

07/07/2021 - 31/12/2021 Madrid, Spain

SOFTWARE DEVELOPERS AMAZON BUSINESS

Develop a personal project to automate the manual tasks done by the person in charge of the on call ticket resolution.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

09/09/2017 - 21/07/2021 Madrid, Spain

SOFTWARE ENGINEER E.T.S.I.S.I Universidad Politécnica de Madrid

Address Madrid, Spain | Website https://www.etsisi.upm.es/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **SPANISH**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C2	C2	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user